

# **BRANDON GUERRERO**

bguerrero5@hotmail.com | 928-315-5126 | San Luis, AZ 85349

## Summary

Hardworking and reliable IT professional with a strong ability to provide technical support for enduser via remote support tools and performs security administration functions for users and remote access. Offering experience in network configuration, wireless network administration, and developing Python web applications.

# Experience

#### **IT Support Specialist**

01/2017 - Current

Gadsden Elementary School District No. 32 | San Luis, AZ

- Provide end-user technical remote support for a district staff of over 800 employees.
- Review requests for services to resolve IT difficulties, documenting solutions to improve future problem resolution.
- Set up computer systems and peripherals for district employees, loading required software and server permissions.
- Maintained inventory of IT assets by checking and documenting locations regularly.
- Consult with vendors to obtain replacement hardware or software and escalate more complex concerns.
- Support, manage and develop python web applications to improve work-flow and performance.
- Manage Google Admin Console accounts and applications regularly to mitigate service interruption.
- Regularly perform maintenance on computer systems to keep optimum performance.
- Manage Windows Active Directory user accounts and computer organizational units to keep an organized system.
- Secure wireless network systems by establishing and enforcing access control
  policies.
- Outlined work plans, assessed resources, and determining timelines for projects.

#### **Licensed Representative**

10/2019 - Current

Independent Insurance Broker | Yuma, AZ

- Promote health insurance to Medicare beneficiaries, analyze the financial viability and productivity of insurance policies for the clients.
- Improve savings margin by enrolling members in the most appropriate health insurance policy and helping members acquire additional benefits at a low or no cost.

#### **Warrants Records Intern**

01/2018 - 05/2018

Yuma County Sherriff's County Yuma, AZ

- Reviewed new and existing arrest warrants, promoting smooth data gathering, and data accuracy.
- Destroy files and materials upon request using the Arizona Department of Public Safety methods and regulations to prevent data breaches.

### Education

**B.S.** Intelligence Studies/Public Administration and Justice Studies Northern Arizona University | Flagstaff, AZ

2018

#### Skills

- Python
- JavaScript
- HTML

Teamwork

- Multitask
- Bilingual (English & Spanish)
- Goal Oriented
- Critical Thinking